And let me just say this,
the trust is a vehicle which takes assets and property from one place to another.
It's also the instrument that's gonna set you free.
When you have a trust is not just some pages in a folder,
nor should it be recorded on the public record.
I don't know where that came from. Anywho,
the trust serves one purpose and one purpose only,
which is to hold property that's protected by a bank.
Y'all gotta look at it like this.
Our states is held in a public trust,
so it's protected by the bank,
even from us. But when you have a private trust that you go take to them
and you give them that, they will move the assets for you into that private trust
because that's what you told them to do.
Moving in trust has to be understood,
not only just saying you have a trust,
if you don't know what to do with the trust,
you not really moving in trust.